The Mainprice Deposit
The Mainprice Deposit
- The Chetham/Clowes Deeds, 15th century-19th century; GB/418/E.7.7-E.7.12 & E.8.3-E.8.14; GB/418/Main/2; 747 files; Chetham's Library
  - Documents relating to Le Rydings in Salford, 1438-1730; GB/418/E.8.12B; GB/418/Main/2/12; 28 files; Chetham's Library
    - Assignment to attend the inheritance of messuage, dwelling house, orchard and garden belonging to John Shelmerdine, bankrupt, 4 Jun 1729; GB/418/E.8.12B no 30; GB/418/Main/2/12/23; Chetham's Library
      From Ann Bower of Manchester, spinster, to Samuel Woolmer of Manchester, merchant
    - Lease for six months and release of messuage, dwelling house, orchard and garden belonging to John Shelmerdine, bankrupt, 6 & 7 Jun 1729; GB/418/E.8.12B no 31 & 32; GB/418/Main/2/12/24; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      From Elizabeth Shelmerdine of Salford, widow of John Shelmerdine, dyer and William Blinkhorn of Manchester, hosier, to Ann Bower.
    - Articles of agreement to convey messuage, burgage or dwelling house in Salford to James Chetham, 22 Jul 1729; GB/418/E.8.12B no 33; GB/418/Main/2/12/25; Chetham's Library
      Between Ann Bower of Manchester, spinster and Samuel W[oo]lmer of Manchester, and James Chetham of Smedley
    - Lease for a year and release of a messuage, burgage or dwelling house in Salford, 24 & 25 Sep 1729; GB/418/E.8.12B no 34 & 35; GB/418/Main/2/12/26; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      From Ann Bower and John Shelmerdine to James Chetham of Smedley
    - Assignment of messuage, burgage or dwelling house in Salford in trust for James Chetham of Smedley, 26 Sep 1729; GB/418/E.8.12B no 36; GB/418/Main/2/12/27; Chetham's Library
      Ffrom Samuel Woolmer to Samuel Clowes of Manchester, merchant
    - Quitclaim of messuage, burgage and tenement, orchard and garden in Salford, 14 Oct 1730; GB/418/E.8.12B no 37; GB/418/Main/2/12/28; Chetham's Library
      From Elizabeth Shelmerdine of Salford, widow of John Shelmerdine, linen-dyer, to James Chetham of Smedley
  - Documents relating to land in Salford, 1563-1869; GB/418/E.8.3-4, E.8.8-9, E.8.12A & E.8.14; GB/418/Main/2/13; 197 files; Chetham's Library
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 10 Jul 1563; GB/418/E.8.3 no 1; GB/418/Main/2/13/1; Chetham's Library
      From Sir Edmonde Trafforde of Trafforde and Edmonde his son to Hugh Torkinton of Salford
    - Conveyance of the Lower House and the Crofts in Broughton, 2 Feb 1630; GB/418/E.8.3 no 2; GB/418/Main/2/13/2; Chetham's Library
      From Henry Wrigley of Salford to John Beswick of Manchester
      2 Feb 1629/30
    - Conveyance of land in Broughton, 1 Apr 1629; GB/418/E.8.3 no 3; GB/418/Main/2/13/3; Chetham's Library
      From Humphrey Chetham of Clayton and John Bradshawe of Broughton to John Whitworth of Salford
    - Bargain and sale of land in Broughton, 20 Jul 1631; GB/418/E.8.3 no 4; GB/418/Main/2/13/4; Chetham's Library
      From Edward Tally, minister at Manchester, Joseph Costerdine of Blakeley (Blackley), John Beswick of Manchester and John Bradshawe of Broughton to William Leaver of Kersal
    - Quitclaim of land in Broughton, 13 Aug 1631; GB/418/E.8.3 no 5; GB/418/Main/2/13/5; Chetham's Library
      From John Whitworth of Salford to John Bradshawe of Broughton
    - Conveyance of land in Salford belonging to Myles Gathorne, 2 May 1635; GB/418/E.8.3 no 6; GB/418/Main/2/13/6; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Torkinton of Rinmore or Ridgmore in Devon to Henry Wrigley of Chambeth in Oldham
    - Mortgage of land in Salford, 12 Jul 1650; GB/418/E.8.3 no 7; GB/418/Main/2/13/7; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Torkinton to Anne Booth
    - Release of land in Salford, 3 Sep 1652; GB/418/E.8.3 no 8; GB/418/Main/2/13/8; Chetham's Library
      From Robert Ridge, Ann Roscowe, George Pie and Alice Pie to Henry Wrigley
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 4 Sep 1654; GB/418/E.8.3 no 9; GB/418/Main/2/13/9; Chetham's Library
      From Edward Warren of Pointon to Henry Wrigley
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 6 Sep 1654; GB/418/E.8.3 no 10; GB/418/Main/2/13/10; Chetham's Library
      From Frances Torkinton of Rinmore to Joshua Wrigley of Chamber
    - Conveyance of Gravel Hole in Salford, 12 Jun 1691; GB/418/E.8.3 no 11; GB/418/Main/2/13/11; Chetham's Library
      From Mary Stott of Salford to James Percival of Salford
    - Mortgage for 99 years of land in Salford, 10 Jan 1707; GB/418/E.8.3 no 12; GB/418/Main/2/13/12; Chetham's Library
      From Anne Wolfenden to Thomas Sanderson
      10 Jan 1706/7
    - Administrators of Anne Woolfenden of Salford, 10 Feb 1707; GB/418/E.8.3 no 13; GB/418/Main/2/13/13; Chetham's Library
      10 Feb 1706/7
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 2 May 1710; GB/418/E.8.3 no 14; GB/418/Main/2/13/14; Chetham's Library
      From Edward Crowther of Salford to James Bayley of Manchester
    - Bond for performance of covenants, 2 May 1710; GB/418/E.8.3 no 15; GB/418/Main/2/13/15; Chetham's Library
    - Will of Ann Wolfenden of Salford, 10 Sep 1712; GB/418/E.8.3 no 16; GB/418/Main/2/13/16; Chetham's Library
    - Conveyance of Gravel Hole in Salford, 29 Jul 1713; GB/418/E.8.3 no 17; GB/418/Main/2/13/17; Chetham's Library
      From Edward Crowther of Salford, Daniel Woolmer of Manchester, John Hepwood, William Hulme and Richard Holde of Manchester to Peter Chaddak of Salford
    - Abstract of title of Henry Dickinson's writings relating to lands in Salford, 1715; GB/418/E.8.3 no 18; GB/418/Main/2/13/18; Chetham's Library
    - Grant and release of land in Salford, 9 May 1723; GB/418/E.8.3 no 19; GB/418/Main/2/13/19; Chetham's Library
      From Alexander Davies of Sidney Sussex Coll and Edward Davies of Manchester to Elizabeth Shelmerdine of Salford
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 14 Feb 1723; GB/418/E.8.3 no 20; GB/418/Main/2/13/20; Chetham's Library
      From Ellin Saxon of Salford to Nathaniel Eaton of Manchester
      14 Feb 1722/3
    - Agreement concerning land in Salford, 8 May 1723; GB/418/E.8.3 no 21; GB/418/Main/2/13/21; Chetham's Library
      Between Alexander Davie of Sidney Sussex College, Cambridge and Shelmerdine of Salford
    - Lease of land in Salford, 9 May 1723; GB/418/E.8.3 no 22; GB/418/Main/2/13/22; Chetham's Library
      From Alexander and Edward Davies to Peter Hamilton
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 25 Apr 1730; GB/418/E.8.3 no 23; GB/418/Main/2/13/23; Chetham's Library
      From Peter Hamilton of Salford to John Kay of Salford
    - Bargain and sale of land in Greengate, Salford, 14 Oct 1730; GB/418/E.8.3 no 24; GB/418/Main/2/13/24; Chetham's Library
      From Elizabeth Shelmerdine of Salford to James Chetham of Smedley
    - Conveyance of lands in Salford, 15 Oct 1730; GB/418/E.8.3 no 25; GB/418/Main/2/13/25; Chetham's Library
      From Elizabeth Shelderdine of Salford to James Chetham of Smedley
    - Agreement concerning land in Salford belonging to James Chetham, 6 Aug 1731; GB/418/E.8.3 no 26; GB/418/Main/2/13/26; Chetham's Library
      Between James Chetham and John Stretch
    - Bond in £100, 23 Jul 1737; GB/418/E.8.3 no 27; GB/418/Main/2/13/27; Chetham's Library
      From Peter Hamilton of Salford to James Chetham of Smedley
    - Conveyance of lands in Salford, 23 Jul 1737; GB/418/E.8.3 no 28; GB/418/Main/2/13/28; Chetham's Library
      From John Kay of Salford to Peter Hamilton of Salford
    - Will of Peter Chaddocke of Salford, surgeon, 13 Dec 1739; GB/418/E.8.3 no 29; GB/418/Main/2/13/29; Chetham's Library
      Attested copy proposed in 1745
    - Assignment of mortgage of land in Salford, 1 Nov 1745; GB/418/E.8.3 no 30; GB/418/Main/2/13/30; Chetham's Library
      From Mary Cooke of Pendlebury, executrix of will of Robert Cooke of Worsley to Robert Dukinfield
    - Conveyanceof land in Salford, 25 Mar 1786; GB/418/E.8.3 no 31, 32 & 33; GB/418/Main/2/13/31; 3 items; Chetham's Library
      From Samuel Clowes to Richard Sandford
      With 2 duplicates
    - Abstract of deeds relating to the title of Jonathan Beever et al to estate in Broughton, Early 19th century; GB/418/E.8.3 no 34; GB/418/Main/2/13/32; Chetham's Library
    - Probate of will of Samuell Clowes of Sprotborough Hall, co Yorks, 5 Nov 1811; GB/418/E.8.3 no 35; GB/418/Main/2/13/33; Chetham's Library
    - Lease of land in Nantwich, 1 Jan 1824; GB/418/E.8.3 no 36; GB/418/Main/2/13/34; Chetham's Library
      From James Hall of Manchester and James Leigh of Ardwick to Thomas Darwell of Manchester
    - Transfer of land in Nantwich, 2 Jan 1824; GB/418/E.8.3 no 37; GB/418/Main/2/13/35; Chetham's Library
    - One inch OS map of Manchester area (sheet 88), 1843; GB/418/E.8.3 no 38; GB/418/Main/2/13/36; Chetham's Library
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 8 Mar 1656; GB/418/E.8.4 no 28; GB/418/Main/2/13/37; Chetham's Library
      From Henry Dickeninson of Manchester and Jane his wife (late wife of Adam Pilkington of Salford) to Thomas Pilkington of Salford
      8 Mar 1655/6
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 14 Apr 1659; GB/418/E.8.4 no 29; GB/418/Main/2/13/38; Chetham's Library
      From Thomas Pilkington of Salford, gent, to Henry Dickinson of Manchester, linendraper
    - Mortgage of a property called Sandywell, 15 Apr 1659; GB/418/E.8.4 no 30; GB/418/Main/2/13/39; Chetham's Library
      From Thomas Pilkington of Salford to Henry Dickinson of Manchester
      Term: 99 years on payment of £6
    - Mortgage of a property called Sandywell and Greenfield, 8 Oct 1678; GB/418/E.8.4 no 31; GB/418/Main/2/13/40; Chetham's Library
      From John and Ann Pilkington to Alexander Davie
    - Lease and release of land in Salford, 16 & 17 Jan 1679; GB/418/E.8.4 no 32 & 33; GB/418/Main/2/13/41; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      From John Pilkington to Thomas Dickinson
      16 & 17 Jan 1678/9
    - Mortgage of Sandywell and Greenfield, 8 Feb 1679; GB/418/E.8.4 no 34; GB/418/Main/2/13/42; Chetham's Library
      From John Pilkington of Worcester and Ann his mother to Alexander Davie of Salford
      8 Feb 1678/9
    - Release of land in Salford, 7 Aug 1679; GB/418/E.8.4 no 35; GB/418/Main/2/13/43; Chetham's Library
      From Ann Pilkington of Worcester to Thomas Dickinson of Salford
    - Receipt for £240, 17 Jan 1680; GB/418/E.8.4 no 36; GB/418/Main/2/13/44; Chetham's Library
      From John Pilkington of Worcester to Alexander Davie of Manchester
      17 Jan 1679/80
    - Declaration by Thomas Dickinson concerning money paid by Alexander Davie to John Pilkington., 17 Jan 1680; GB/418/E.8.4 no 37; GB/418/Main/2/13/45; Chetham's Library
      31 Mar 1680
    - Lease of land in Salford, 14 Jan 1681; GB/418/E.8.4 no 38; GB/418/Main/2/13/46; Chetham's Library
      From Thomas Dickinson to Alexander Davie
      14 Jan 1680/81
    - Declaration by Thomas Dickinson concerning tenure of land in Salford by Alexander Davie, 15 Jan 1681; GB/418/E.8.4 no 39; GB/418/Main/2/13/47; Chetham's Library
      15 Jan 1680/81
    - Conveyance of land in Broughton, 26 Apr 1683; GB/418/E.8.4 no 40; GB/418/Main/2/13/48; Chetham's Library
      From Ferdinando Stanley of Whit[t]le in Bury to Alexander Davy of Salford
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 15 Oct 1703; GB/418/E.8.4 no 41; GB/418/Main/2/13/49; Chetham's Library
      From Nathaniel Jenkinson and John Ainsworth to Alexander Davie
    - Bond for £62, 16 Oct 1703; GB/418/E.8.4 no 42; GB/418/Main/2/13/50; Chetham's Library
      From Nathaniel Jenkinson of Manchester and John Ainsworth of Westminster to Alexander Davie
    - Lease of land in Salford, 2 Dec 1718; GB/418/E.8.4 no 43; GB/418/Main/2/13/51; Chetham's Library
      From Alexander Davie to Robert Alsop
    - Mortgage by way of release, 3 Dec 1718; GB/418/E.8.4 no 44; GB/418/Main/2/13/52; Chetham's Library
      From Alexander Davie to Robert Alsop of land in Salford
    - Articles for sale of lands and estates in Salford, 1 Sep 1722; GB/418/E.8.4 no 45; GB/418/Main/2/13/53; Chetham's Library
      From Alexander Davie to Edward Davie
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 30 Oct 1722; GB/418/E.8.4 no 46; GB/418/Main/2/13/54; Chetham's Library
      From Edward Davie of Manchester to George Chetham of Smedley
    - Release of land in Salford, 21 Feb 1723; GB/418/E.8.4 no 47; GB/418/Main/2/13/55; Chetham's Library
      21 Feb 1722/3
    - Release of land in Salford, 29 Mar 1723; GB/418/E.8.4 no 48; GB/418/Main/2/13/56; Chetham's Library
      From Alexander Davie and Edward Davie to George Chetham
    - Articles of agreement concerning land in Salford, 30 Oct 1722; GB/418/E.8.4 no 49; GB/418/Main/2/13/57; Chetham's Library
      Between George Chetham and Edward Davie
    - Deed of uses of a fine levied by Alexander and Edward Davie of land in Salford, 24 Jun 1723; GB/418/E.8.4 no 50; GB/418/Main/2/13/58; Chetham's Library
    - Deed of uses of a fine levied by Alexander and Henry Davie of land in Salford, 24 Jun 1723; GB/418/E.8.4 no 51; GB/418/Main/2/13/59; Chetham's Library
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 28 Sep 1723; GB/418/E.8.4 no 52; GB/418/Main/2/13/60; Chetham's Library
      From Edward Davie to George Chetham
    - Abstract of title to land in Broughton and Chetham, property of Lawrence Rawstorne, [?1744]; GB/418/E.8.4 no 53; GB/418/Main/2/13/61; Chetham's Library
    - Final concord, nd; GB/418/E.8.4 no [54]; GB/418/Main/2/13/62; Chetham's Library
      Largely illegible
    - Will of William Hawet of Manchester, 12 Jun 1696; GB/418/E.8.7(a) no 1; GB/418/Main/2/13/63; Chetham's Library
      [NB This will does not appear in published indices of Chester wills.]
    - Bargain and sale of land in Salford, 23 Jun 1714; GB/418/E.8.7(a) no 2; GB/418/Main/2/13/64; Chetham's Library
      From Richard Hawett of Liverpool, merchant to Thomas Peacock
    - Release of lands in Salford, 24 Jun 1714; GB/418/E.8.7(a) no 3; GB/418/Main/2/13/65; Chetham's Library
      From Richard Hawett of Liverpool to Thomas Peacock
    - Deed poll, 29 Jul 1714; GB/418/E.8.7(a) no 4; GB/418/Main/2/13/66; Chetham's Library
      From James Edge of Manchester to Thomas Peacock
    - Will of Thomas Peacock of Salford, feltmaker, 15 Oct 1714; GB/418/E.8.7(a) no 5; GB/418/Main/2/13/67; Chetham's Library
    - Lease and release of land in Salford, 1 & 2 May 1717; GB/418/E.8.7(a) no 6 & 7; GB/418/Main/2/13/68; Chetham's Library
      From James Edge of Manchester to Daniel Hulme
    - Grant of way in Back Salford, 25 Apr 1728; GB/418/E.8.7(a) no 8; GB/418/Main/2/13/69; Chetham's Library
      From Robert Booth to James Edge and Daniel Hulme
    - Copy will of Daniel Hulme of Salford, feltmaker, 25 May 1729; GB/418/E.8.7(a) no 9; GB/418/Main/2/13/70; Chetham's Library
    - Grant and release of lands in Salford, 19 Mar 1737; GB/418/E.8.7(a) no 10; GB/418/Main/2/13/71; Chetham's Library
      From James Grantham to Thomas Isherwood
    - Conveyance of lands in Salford, 10 Mar 1738; GB/418/E.8.7(a) no 11; GB/418/Main/2/13/72; Chetham's Library
      From Thomas Usherwood of Salford et al to James Chetham
    - Agreement concerning land in Salford, 25 Oct 1737; GB/418/E.8.7(a) no 12; GB/418/Main/2/13/73; Chetham's Library
      Between Thomas Usherwood of Salford, clockmaker, and James Chetham of Smedley
    - Abstract of title deeds of Thomas Usherwood, [?c 1715]; GB/418/E.8.7(a) no 13; GB/418/Main/2/13/74; Chetham's Library
    - Account from Christopher Byron to James Chetham, 27 Oct 1737; GB/418/E.8.7(a) no 14; GB/418/Main/2/13/75; Chetham's Library
    - Letter from [?] Brownswood to Christopher Byron, 6 Mar 1738; GB/418/E.8.7(a) no 15; GB/418/Main/2/13/76; Chetham's Library
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 15 Jul 1707; GB/418/E.8.8 no 1; GB/418/Main/2/13/77; Chetham's Library
      From Esther Marler, Samuel Eaton, Dorothy Eaton and Marler Eaton to John Starkey
    - Assignment of Edward Crowther's lease of land in Salford to James Bayley, 2 Nov 1711; GB/418/E.8.8 no 2; GB/418/Main/2/13/78; Chetham's Library
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 30 Jul 1713; GB/418/E.8.8 no 3; GB/418/Main/2/13/79; Chetham's Library
      From Edward Crowther to Peter Chaddock
    - Bond in £600 for performance of covenants, 30 Jul 1713; GB/418/E.8.8 no 4; GB/418/Main/2/13/80; Chetham's Library
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 30 Jul 1713; GB/418/E.8.8 no 5; GB/418/Main/2/13/81; Chetham's Library
      From Frances Davenport to Robert Cooke
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 8 Feb 1729; GB/418/E.8.8 no 6; GB/418/Main/2/13/82; Chetham's Library
      From Peter Chaddock of Salford to Robert Cooke of Worsley
    - Lease for one year, 30 Oct 1745; GB/418/E.8.8 no 7; GB/418/Main/2/13/83; Chetham's Library
      From Ralph Banks and Richard Whitehead to James Chetham of land in Salford
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 31 Oct 1745; GB/418/E.8.8 no 8; GB/418/Main/2/13/84; Chetham's Library
      From Ralph Banks and Richard Whitehead of Salford to James Chetham
    - Lease of land in Harwood, 20 Jan 1775; GB/418/E.8.8 no 9; GB/418/Main/2/13/85; Chetham's Library
      From Richard Lomax of Harwood to Benjamin Bentley of Elton
    - Grant and demise of chief rent of £112[?] 0s 10d payable on estate in Salford, 25 Mar 1808; GB/418/E.8.8 no 10; GB/418/Main/2/13/86; Chetham's Library
      From Samuel Clowes to William Eccles and John Coupe
    - Conveyance of land in Kersal, 31 Oct 1827; GB/418/E.8.8 no 11; GB/418/Main/2/13/87; Chetham's Library
      From Rev John Clowes to James Leicester
    - Release in fee of land in Salford, 30 Jun 1837; GB/418/E.8.8 no 12; GB/418/Main/2/13/88; Chetham's Library
      From Rev John Clowes to John Whitlow
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 25 Feb 1724; GB/418/E.8.8 no 13; GB/418/Main/2/13/89; Chetham's Library
      From James Danson of Salford to George Chadwick
    - Copy of conveyance of land in Salford, 12 Jul 1717; GB/418/E.8.8 no 14; GB/418/Main/2/13/90; Chetham's Library
      From John Hill of London, merchant to James Dawson of Salford
    - Copy of conveyance of land in Salford, 13 Jul 1717; GB/418/E.8.8 no 15; GB/418/Main/2/13/91; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      From John Hill of London to James Dawson of Salford
      Two copies
    - Copy will of Samuel Haward of Salford, chapman, 3 Jul 1704; GB/418/E.8.8 no 16; GB/418/Main/2/13/92; Chetham's Library
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 19 Sep 1724; GB/418/E.8.8 no 17; GB/418/Main/2/13/93; Chetham's Library
      From George Chadwick of Dukinfield to James Dawson of Salford
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 2 Jun 1724; GB/418/E.8.8 no 18; GB/418/Main/2/13/94; Chetham's Library
    - Abstract of writings rec[eive]d from Mr Dawson and Mr Hawarth relating to a house in Dawson's Croft in Salford, [?1731]; GB/418/E.8.8 no 19; GB/418/Main/2/13/95; Chetham's Library
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 7 Nov 1756; GB/418/E.8.8 no 20; GB/418/Main/2/13/96; Chetham's Library
      From George Chadwick of Pepperhill in Sale to Ann Chetham of Smedley
    - Lease and release of land in Salford, 24 & 25 Feb 1724; GB/418/E.8.8 no 21; GB/418/Main/2/13/97; Chetham's Library
      From James Dawson to George Chadwick
    - Assignment of land in Salford in trust for James Chetham, 16 Aug 1739; GB/418/E.8.8 no 22; GB/418/Main/2/13/98; Chetham's Library
      From James Dawson and Abraham Hawarth to Samuel Clowes
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 8 Nov 1755; GB/418/E.8.8 no 23; GB/418/Main/2/13/99; Chetham's Library
      From George Chadwick to Ann Chetham
    - Lease for one year of land in Salford, 26 Mar 1807; GB/418/E.8.8 no 24; GB/418/Main/2/13/100; Chetham's Library
      From Martha Clowes to Samuel Clowes et al
    - Probate of will of Samuel Clowes, 2 Nov 1790; GB/418/E.8.8 no 25; GB/418/Main/2/13/101; Chetham's Library
    - Conveyance of houses in Salford, 10 Mar 1734; GB/418/E.8.8 no 26; GB/418/Main/2/13/102; Chetham's Library
      From James Edge to James Chetham
    - Bargain and sale of land in Manchester, 15 Feb 1712; GB/418/E.8.9 no 1; GB/418/Main/2/13/103; Chetham's Library
      From George Berhnshaw of Manchester to Richard Richardson of Salford
      15 Feb 1711/12
    - Bargain and sale of land in Salford, 28 Mar 1723; GB/418/E.8.9 no 2; GB/418/Main/2/13/104; Chetham's Library
    - Bargain and sale of land in Salford, 8 May 1723; GB/418/E.8.9 no 3; GB/418/Main/2/13/105; Chetham's Library
      From Alexander Davie of Sidney Sussex College to Pete Hamilton of Salford
    - Bargain and sale of land in Salford, 27 Sep 1723; GB/418/E.8.9 no 4; GB/418/Main/2/13/106; Chetham's Library
      From Edward Davie of Manchester to George Chetham of Manchester
    - Bargain and sale of tithes of Westhoughton, 1 Sep 1724; GB/418/E.8.9 no 5; GB/418/Main/2/13/107; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Colston of St. Andrews Holborne of Middlesex to William Legh of Westhoughton
    - Bargain and sale of land in Manchester, 9 Sep 1729; GB/418/E.8.9 no 6; GB/418/Main/2/13/108; Chetham's Library
      From William Walker of Manchester, Samuel Clowes and Thomas Clowes
    - Bargain and sale of land in Salford, 24 Apr 1730; GB/418/E.8.9 no 7; GB/418/Main/2/13/109; Chetham's Library
    - Bond in £300, 25 Apr 1730; GB/418/E.8.9 no 8; GB/418/Main/2/13/110; Chetham's Library
      From Peter Hamilton of Salford, James Holt of Tottington and Edward Hold of Manchester to John Kay of Salford
    - Bargain and sale of land in Salford, 23 May 1735; GB/418/E.8.9 no 9; GB/418/Main/2/13/111; Chetham's Library
      From John Fletcher of Manchester, John Widdows of Manchester and Thomas Gathorne to James Chetham of Smedley
    - Bargain and sale of land in Salford, 22 Jul 1737; GB/418/E.8.9 no 10; GB/418/Main/2/13/112; Chetham's Library
      From John Kay of Salford and Peter Hamilton of Salford to James Chetham of Smedley
    - Bargain and sale of land in Salford, 9 Mar 1739; GB/418/E.8.9 no 11; GB/418/Main/2/13/113; Chetham's Library
      From Hugh Parr of Salford to James Chetham of Smedley
      9 Mar 1738/39
    - Marriage settlement, 20 Mar 1746; GB/418/E.8.9 no 12; GB/418/Main/2/13/114; Chetham's Library
      Between William Harrison of Manchester and Ann Stockport of Manchester
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 8 May 1554; GB/418/E.8.9, bdl 11, no 1; GB/418/Main/2/13/115; Chetham's Library
      From Henry Ince and Katherine his wife to Thomas Mavecroft and Elizabeth his wife and Peter Seddon and Alice his wife
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 2 Mar 1579; GB/418/E.8.9, bdl 11, no 2; GB/418/Main/2/13/116; Chetham's Library
      From Raphe Seddon to Pilkington to Elizabeth Williamson of Salford
    - Copy of will of Robert Booth of Salford, 1 May 1709; GB/418/E.8.9, bdl 11, no 3; GB/418/Main/2/13/117; Chetham's Library
    - Copy of will of Humphrey Booth of Salford, 19 Dec 1723; GB/418/E.8.9, bdl 11, no 4; GB/418/Main/2/13/118; Chetham's Library
    - Grant and release of land in Salford, 29 Jan 1726; GB/418/E.8.9, bdl 11, no 5; GB/418/Main/2/13/119; Chetham's Library
      From Robert Booth of Salford to Hugh Parr of Salford
      29 Jan 1725/6
    - Bargain and sale of land in Salford, 25 May 1727; GB/418/E.8.9, bdl 11, no 6; GB/418/Main/2/13/120; Chetham's Library
      From William Seddon of Prestlee to Hugh Parr of Salford
    - Bargain and sale of land in Salford, 28 May 1727; GB/418/E.8.9, bdl 11, no 7; GB/418/Main/2/13/121; Chetham's Library
    - Deed to lead uses of a fine of orchard in Salford, 25 Jul 1727; GB/418/E.8.9, bdl 11, no 8; GB/418/Main/2/13/122; Chetham's Library
      From Hugh Parr of Salford to John Walker of Salford
    - Conveyance of land in Salford, 10 Mar 1739; GB/418/E.8.9, bdl 11, no 9; GB/418/Main/2/13/123; Chetham's Library
      10 Mar 1738/9
    - Assignment of a term to attend inheritance of garden in Salford, 12 Mar 1739; GB/418/E.8.9, bdl 11, no 10; GB/418/Main/2/13/124; Chetham's Library
      From Alice Edge to Samuel Clowes in trust for James Chetham
      12 Mar 1738/9
    - Schedule of documents, 18th century; GB/418/E.8.9, bdl 11, no 11; GB/418/Main/2/13/125; Chetham's Library